const STORE = {
    questions: [
        {
            question: "What is the name of the town where the story takes place?",
            options: [
                'Hulk Town',
                'Riverdale',
                'Hawkins',
                'Springfield'
            ],
            answer: 'Hawkins'
        },
        {
            question: "Who is the girl with telekinetic abilities?",
            options: [
                'Susie',
                'Twelve', 
                'Maxine',
                'Eleven'
            ],
            answer: 'Eleven'
        },
        {
            question: "Who is the boy that goes missing in the first season?",
            options: [
                'Will Byers',
                'Jim Hopper',
                'Bugs Bunny', 
                'Mike Wheeler'
            ],
            answer: 'Will Byers'
        },
        {
            question: "What decade does the story take place?",
            options: [
                '1990s',
                '1980s',
                '2010s',
                '1940s'
            ],
            answer: '1980s'
        },
        {
            question: "What do the kids call the place where Will was taken to in the first season?",
            options: [
                'The Upside Down',
                'The Backwards Upwards',
                'ToonTown',
                'New York'
            ],
            answer: 'The Upside Down'
        },
        {
            question: "Where does Steve work in season 3?",
            options: [
                "Scoops and more Scoops!", 
                "Scoops Ahoy!",
                "Taco Bell",
                "Hawkin’s Post"
            ],
            answer: 'Scoops Ahoy!'
        },
        {
            question: "What is the name of the creature the characters face in the first season?",
            options: [
                'The Mind Flayer',
                'Bowser',
                'The Demogorgon',
                'Lord Voldemort'
            ],
            answer: 'THe Demogorgon'
        },
        {
            question: "What is the name of the game the four boys would play in Mike’s basement?",
            options: [
                'Dungeons and Dragons',
                'Mario Party',
                'Connect Four',
                'Twister'
            ],
            answer: 'Dungeons and Dragons'
        },
        {
            question: "Who do the four boys dress up as for Halloween in the second season?",
            options: [
                'The Three Stooges',
                'The Avengers',
                'The Scooby Doo gang',
                'The Ghostbusters'
            ],
            answer: 'The Ghostbusters'
        },
        {
            question: "How does Joye Byers communicate with her missing son in the first season?",
            options: [
                'A Ouija board',
                'Christmas lights',
                'Postcards',
                'Telegram'
            ],
            answer: 'Christmas lights'
        }
    ],
    currentQuestion: 0,
    score: 0,
};